Olalekan Adebanjo

Phone number: (+234) 8088643372 (Mobile) | Email address: oadebanjo99@gmail.com | Website:

https://thefirstportfolio1.netlify.app/ | LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/olalekan-adebanjo-820633264 | Gith

ub: https://github.com/olalekan99 | **Address:** Lagos, Nigeria (Home)

ABOUT ME

A dedicated Software Engineer with one year experience looking forward to acquiring more tech skills, growing and making a great impact in the tech space. Also passionate about impacting knowledge, growth in the society having great listening and administrative skills.

WORK EXPERIENCE

03/2023 - 08/2023 Lagos, Nigeria

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER SAIL INNOVATION LAB (TRAINEE)

- Participated in a team project to build a learning management system (LMS) which is scalable and well integrated.
- Modularized and refactored the codebase to make it more readable and clean.
- Created mongo database thereby creating endpoints
- Validated the endpoints before transferring to frontend developers
- Created a simple single pager commercial web application using Html, CSS and JavaScript.
- Utilized Html, CSS and JavaScript to create a responsive landing page.
- Maintained graphical standard throughout the project

10/2022 - 11/2022 Lagos, Nigeria

FRONTEND DEVELOPER ZURI COHORT BOOT CAMP (TRAINEE)

- Created an alumni school website using Html, CSS in a team project.
- · Used GIT and GITHUB to build and share data
- Collaborated with my team to designers and developers to ship in new features suing the best practices.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

08/2009 - 09/2014 Ogun, Nigeria

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE, BIOCHEMISTRY Olabisi Onabanjo University

08/2022 - 09/2022 Lagos, Nigeria

CERTIFICATE IN WEB DEVELOPMENT Nigeria German Center (GIZ)

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): **ENGLISH** | **YORUBA**

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

OTHER EXPERIENCE

01/2018 - 03/2022

Martwayne School of Fashion, Lagos State, Nigeria.

Trainer

- Charged with impacting fashion knowledge, technical know how and starting up to clients .
- Assisted and executed administrative duties in the establishment.
- Contributed to the day to day development of g establishment and clients.
- Boost the moral and ethics of the trainee thereby increasing the attendance and interest in the skill.

SKILLS

Skills

- HTML5
- CSS
- JavaScript
- React IS
- Node IS
- Mongo DB
- GIT
- GitHub

PROJECTS

08/2023

Learning Management System (LMS) Application of HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React JS, Node JS, Mongo DB... https://github.com/Baouldguyd/ssmp-app-backend

12/2022

Alumni Website generators for tertiary Institution Application of HTML5, CSS, JavaScript https://github.com/zuri-training/TeamDugong

AWARD

Nigeria German Center (GIZ) / Weevil, 2022.

Best Trainee in the Weevil Company/ GIZ one month Programmer in Frontend Development (Html & CSS)